- What up, dawg?
- Ciara, Ciara!
- What?
- Jazze Pha's on the phone.
- Hello?
- Hey, CC.
- What up?
- We going to the car wash tonight, baby,
we going to get blinged up.
- All right, I'ma see you up there.
- 'Sho nuff!
- [Ciara] Hey, hey, make
sure you stay out of my room.
- Bye!
♪ My goodies, my goodies,
my goodies, not my goodies ♪
♪ Listen, I got a sick
reputation for handling broads ♪
♪ All I need is me a few seconds or more ♪
♪ And it's a wrap, tell
valet to bring my 'Lac ♪
♪ And I ain't coming back ♪
♪ So you can put a car right there ♪
♪ I'm the truth, and I
ain't got nothing to prove ♪
♪ And you can ask anybody ♪
♪ 'Cause they seen me do it ♪
♪ Barricades, I run right
through them, used to them ♪
♪ Throw all the dirt you
want, there's no use ♪
♪ You still won't have a
pent up in a fabulous room ♪
♪ (censored) her back, picking
out a basket of fruit ♪
♪ I love you, boo ♪
♪ Yeah, Freaky Petey love you too ♪
♪ You know how I do, that goodie goodie ♪
♪ You may look at me and think
that I'm just a young girl ♪
♪ But I'm not just a young girl ♪
♪ Baby, this is what I'm looking for ♪
♪ A sexy, independent,
down to spend it type ♪
♪ That's getting his dough ♪
♪ I'm not being too dramatic ♪
♪ That's the way I gotta have it ♪
♪ I bet you want the goodies ♪
♪ Bet you thought about it ♪
♪ Got you all hot and bothered ♪
♪ Mad 'cause I talk around it ♪
♪ If you're looking for the goodies ♪
♪ Keep on looking, 'cause
they stay in the jar ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Just because you drive a Benz
I'm not going home with you ♪
♪ You won't get no nookie or
the cookies, I'm no rookie ♪
♪ If you ain't sexy,
independent, I ain't with it ♪
♪ So you already know ♪
♪ I'm not being too dramatic ♪
♪ That's the way I gotta have it ♪
♪ You may talk slick, trying to hit ♪
♪ But I'm not dumb ♪
♪ I'm not being too dramatic ♪
♪ It's just how I gotta have it ♪
♪ I bet you want the goodies ♪
♪ Bet you thought about it ♪
♪ Got you all hot and bothered ♪
♪ Mad 'cause I talk around it ♪
♪ If you're looking for the goodies ♪
♪ Keep on looking, 'cause
they stay in the jar ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah ♪
♪ Wait a minute ♪
♪ So damn hot, but so young ♪
♪ You ain't got milk on your
tongue, slow down, little one ♪
♪ We ain't got long ♪
♪ Hey, shorty, ya both play the game ♪
♪ You think you bad, but you ain't bad ♪
♪ I'll show you what bad is ♪
♪ Bad is when you capable
of beating the baddest ♪
♪ I've been working at it ever
since I came to this planet ♪
♪ I ain't quite there yet,
but I'm getting better at it ♪
♪ Matter of fact, let me tell
it to you one more again ♪
♪ All I got to do is
tell a girl who I am ♪
♪ Ain't ne'er chick in
here that I can't have ♪
♪ Bada-Boom, bada-bam, ba-bam ♪
♪ You're insinuating that I'm hot ♪
♪ But these goodies, boy, are not ♪
♪ Just for any of the many men ♪
♪ That's trying to get on top ♪
♪ No, you can't call me later ♪
♪ And I don't want your number ♪
♪ I'm not changing stories ♪
♪ Just respect the play I'm calling ♪
♪ I bet you want the goodies ♪
♪ Bet you thought about it ♪
♪ Got you all hot and bothered ♪
♪ Mad 'cause I talk about it ♪
♪ If you're looking for the goodies ♪
♪ Keep on looking, 'cause
they stay in the jar ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, yeah ♪